Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Peck School of the Arts, 1936-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee Peck School of the Arts, Office of the Dean Records, 1936-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Peck School of the Arts. Office of the Dean
UWM Archival Collection 81
Accession 2016-008
22.2 cubic ft. (27 boxes including 5 audio reels) 1 oversize folder 2 digital text files (3 MB) Plus additions of 16.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes) and 20 digital text files (0.336 MB)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of the deans of the school and records of the departments that preceded the school's creation in 1963. Consists largely of correspondence with the school's departments of Film, Theatre and Dance, Art, and Music and with visiting artists concerning curriculum, budgeting and events planning. Contains meeting minutes, affirmative action material, and minority program and retention material, as well as items on urban services of the school. Also includes posters and programs of art exhibitions and performances. Unrestricted material from search and screen committees concern the hiring of two of the school's deans as well as various faculty positions. Includes calendars published in the 1930s by the Wisconsin Printmakers, an organization of Wisconsin Artists which featured artworks by students and faculty of Milwaukee State Teachers College.
From 1956 (when the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee was established) to 1962, the departments of Music and Art answered to the College of Letters & Science and the School of Education, respectively.
In December 1962, the University of Wisconsin Board of Regents approved the creation of the School of Fine Arts at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. The School of Fine Arts administered the newly created departments of Theatre, Dance, and Film. At the same time, the departments of Music and Art transferred into the School of Fine Arts. In 1982, Theatre and Dance were merged into one department.
In 1998, the school changed its name to School of the Arts, in order to more accurately and expansively describe the activities of the school devoted to the study of the Arts. In 2000, the Milton and Lillian Peck Foundation in 2000 made a grant to allow the school to purchase the Temple Emanu-El B'Ne Jeshurun building (today the Helene Zelazo Center), and as part of the conditions of the grant the school was renamed again, to the Milton and Lillian Peck School of the Arts.
Deans of the School
1962-1974 Adolph A. Suppan
1974-1985 Robert Corrigan
1985 Gerard McKenna (Acting)
1985-1989 Robert Hickock
1989 Corliss Phillabaum (Acting)
1989-1992 James A. Sappenfield (Interim)
1992-1993 Will H. Rockett
1993-1994 Leslie Vansen
1995-1999 Catherine Davy
1999-2001 Robert Greenstreet (interim)
2001-2007 W. Robert Bucker
2007-2008 Scott Emmons (Interim)
2008-2011 Wade Hobgood
2012-2013 Scott Emmons (Interim)
2013- Scott Emmons
Miscellaneous records of the deans of the school as well as records of the departments that preceded the school's creation in 1963. Collection documents the development of curricula, budgeting of the departments and the school at large, planning of events, performances, and art exhibitions. The majority of the records are correspondence sent to or by the dean's office and the departments of Film, Theatre and Dance, Music, and Art. The files also contain agendas, minutes, and supporting materials from departmental ad hoc and standing committees, including the Academic Appeals Committee, the Anonymous Funds Committee, the Budget Advisory Committee, departmental Executive Committees, the Master of Fine Arts Planning Committee, and the Promotion and Tenure Committee.
The files on Affirmative Action (1973-1978) consist of statistics on hiring in the School of Fine Arts and statistical breakdowns of the school's enrollment and fine arts degrees awarded in the United States. These files also include guidelines set by the U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.
There is a folder of items regarding the Artists-In-Residence program. This program brought artists in music, painting, sculpture, dance, theatre, and poetry to UWM. While at the university, the artists would offer performances or exhibitions, engage in informal discussion sessions, and teach short classes in their respective media. The files contain correspondence between the school and the artists as well as some biographies of artists.
The Correspondence files contain the letters to and from the dean with individuals regarding funding, staffing, and policy issues. There are letters to and from artists, prospective faculty and deans of other fine arts schools. There is some overlap in other correspondence items found in committee, departmental, and program files.
Files on the Curriculum Committee contain minutes and agendas. The committee reviewed plans for majors and minors. The committee also reviewed matters regarding course addition or deletion and name changes as well as credit amounts and plans for inter-arts majors.
Fine Arts Quartet files contain performance programs, reviews of performances, and correspondences. The group, which was originally the Fine Arts Quartet of Chicago, joined the UWM faculty in 1963.
The Fine Arts Center opened in 1968 with Inaugural Week of events that included a film festival, a play, several music performances, and a dance concert. These files include event planning, correspondence, programs, and three lectures on audio reels.
Several folders of Posters and Related Materials include event flyers and posters announcing performances, exhibitions, and symposia.
Search and Screen files contain meeting minutes and correspondence of several Search and Screen Committees, concerning the searches for two of the school's deans (in 1974 and 1985) and various faculty and department chair positions.
Several files are included on the University Arts Council, which was involved in the arts activities of the University of Wisconsin System. This council was involved in events planning, administering surveys, and distributing a monthly newsletter to arts programs and schools.
The Wisconsin Artists Calendars were printed in the mid to late 1930s by the Wisconsin Printmakers, an artists' organization which supported the graphic arts. The calendars feature wood and linoleum cuts by artists who were students of the Milwaukee State Teachers College, a predecessor of UWM.
The May 2016 addition to the collection contains administration, program, and exhibition records, including records of development of the Master of Fine Arts program, and records relating to the collaboration between the School of Fine Arts and the Milwaukee Public Schools to offer art classes to MPS students. Also included are records of the People's Theater, a community organization to which the School provided significant financial and administrative support, including shared personnel, between 1968-1988. Much of this recent addition is comprised of folders on the future of the UWM Art Museum, including responses to a proposal to sell some of UWM's art collection.
The files are organized alphabetically by subject, then chronologically.
The collection consists of one additional accession:
Accession 2016-008: Planning Documents, Program Review Files, Accreditation Files, and Subject Files, 1978-2016
An inventory of the personnel files in boxes 10-14 is available in the Archives' case files.
A folder-by-folder inventory of 2016-008, including a spreadsheet containing information on the digital files, is also available in the Archives.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
Fine Arts Quartet Records UWM Manuscript Collection 30
UW-Milwaukee College of Letters & Science Records UWM Archival Collection 1
UW-Milwaukee Department of Dance Records UWM Archival Collection 30
UW-Milwaukee Department of Theatre Records UWM Archival Collection 85
UW-Milwaukee Office of the Provost and Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs Records UWM Archival Collection 12
UW-Milwaukee Photographs Collection UWM Archival Collection 6
UW-Milwaukee School of Education Records UWM Archival Collection 5
Administrative/Restriction Information
The unclassified personnel files in boxes 10-14, as well as the personnel-related files in box 27, are restricted in accordance with UWM Personnel File Policy S-42 and Wis. Stat. 19.36 (10.b). Access is regulated by Section III.A.2 and III.A.3.
The student fellowship records in box 26 are restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) and UW-System RRDA UWSTU046. Access may be granted by permission of the University Records Custodian or pursuant to the terms stipulated in 34 CFR 99.31. Records in Box 26 relating to the sale of Art Museum Assets contain confidential legal advice and are restricted under Wis. Stat. 905.03 (Lawyer-Client Privilege).
There are no access restrictions on the rest of the collection, which is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
An unknown individual transferred the collection to the Archives prior to 1989. Peck School of the Arts transferred accession 2015-041 in April 2016, and accession 2016-008 in August 2016.
As of August 30, 2013, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core 2 Duo CPU (2.33 GHz, 1.95 GB RAM) running Windows XP Professional Version 2002, with Service Pack 3. Adobe Reader XI was used to access the files.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Acrobat PDF 1.6 - Portable Document Format [.pdf]
Open Document Text [.odt]
Open Document Spreadsheet [.ods]
Contents List
- UW-Milwaukee Peck School of the Arts, Office of the Dean Records, 1936-2013, UWM Archival Collection 81; 22.2 cubic ft. (27 boxes including 5 audio reels) 1 oversize folder 2 digital text files (3 MB)
  - Academic Appeals Committee
    - 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1976-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Academic Computing Needs, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Dean's Council, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Planning Committee, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
  - Academic Staff Committee, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - All-Campus Arts Festival, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American National Theatre and Academy, 1963-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ann Arbor Film Festival, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anonymous Funds Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Art Exhibitions Committee, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Artists-in-Residence Program, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Artists-in-Residence Roundtable "The Artist and the University," 1966, Audio reel (¼ in.) (Box 9, Audio 1)
  - Arts and Humanities Executive Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arts Extension, UW-Extension/School of Fine Arts, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Arts in Society, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Asian Art Show, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Assistant to the Dean for Publicity, Elizabeth Earnest, 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Associate Dean Cook, Wayne, General Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Associate Dean Phillabaum, Corliss, General Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Audit of Bachelors and Masters of Fine Arts Programs in UW System, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Bachelor of Arts Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Biennial Budget Advisory Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brochures, 1979-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Budget Advisory Committee
    - 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    - 1975-1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Budget Planning Document
    - 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Business/Fine Arts Building Committee, 1985-1991 (Box 18, Folder 10-12)
  - Calendar, 2008, 2013
  - Calendar Listings
    - 1989-1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 14-16)
  - Calendars of Fine Arts Events, 1966-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Carnicus Project, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Center for Electronic Arts and Culture Proposal, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Center for Twentieth Century Studies, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Centers and Institutes, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Centers of Excellence, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
  - Children's Performing Arts, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committees, School of Fine Arts, 1981-1994 (Box 19, Folder 1-6)
  - Community Arts Programming, 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Community Services, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Community Theatre Institute, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Composer's Showcase, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Computer Study Committee, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Conferences and Workshops, 1955-1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Contemporary Arts Festival, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Coordinating Council for Higher Education, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
  - Correspondence
    - 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
    - 1965-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Corrigan, Robert: Fullbright Award, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Corrigan, Robert, University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, Foundation Reimbursements, 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Creative Writing Department, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Credits to Degree, Memorandums, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Curriculum, 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1962-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
  - Dean's Roundtable on WUWM Radio, 1991-2001 (Box 19, Folder 10-12)
  - Dean's Student Advisory Committee, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Decorative Arts Forum, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Department of Art
    - Audit and Review, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, 1963-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Department of Dance
    - Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Curriculum, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Financial Projections, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - News Releases, 1965-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Department of Music
    - Chairperson Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 23-26)
    - Curriculum, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Executive Committee, 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Department of Theatre and Dance
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Department of Theatre Arts
    - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, 1969-1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1966-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Position Announcements, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Productions, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Departmental Profiles, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Departments of Art Meeting, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Distance Education, UWM, 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Door County Cultural Center Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Downey Book Project, UWM Libraries and Peck School of the Arts, 2000, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Downey Festival in London, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Early Registration System, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Economics in School of Fine Arts, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Education Council, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Engelman Hall Remodeling Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Evening Classes and GER Course Meeting Times, 1966-1996 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Event Announcements and Information, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  - Executive Committee of Arts and Humanities, 1963-1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Expansion Arts and Humanities Program, 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Facilities and Space
    - 1974-1997 (Box 19, Folder 19-21)
    - Fine Arts Center, 1971-1981 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Holton Hall, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Mitchell Hall, 1973-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Faculty and Student Advisory Committee Minutes, 1969-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1963-1981 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
  - Faculty Meetings, Agenda and Minutes, 1969-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Meetings, University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Film Arts Undergraduate Major, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fine Arts Core Curriculum, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fine Arts Education Council
    - 1964-1976 (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fine Arts, Education Jurisdictional Controversy, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fine Arts Events, 1962-1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fine Arts Galleries, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 26-28)
  - Fine Arts Marketing Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fine Arts Quartet
    - Letters and Memos, 1961-1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - News Releases, 1960-1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Programs, 1971-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fine Arts Traveling Groups, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fire Insurance Inventory, 1957-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Four Year Graduation Guarantee, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Gifts, 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gifts to Fine Arts Gallery, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Juris Gotshalks Memorial Fund, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Graduate Program Committee
    - 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1978-1979, 1983-1987, 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Program in Art, Five Year Reviews, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School Fellowship Awards to School of Fine Arts Students, 1979-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    Restricted
  - Graduate Student Special Assistance Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Grand Avenue Mall Proposal, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Growth Projections, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hansberry-Sands Theatre Company, 1981-1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - High School Counselor Breakfast, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Human Relations Code Requirements, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Inaugural Week
    - Critic Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Dance Concert, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Etler Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Catalog, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Films, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Hovhaness Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Imbrie Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Invitation, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Lecture by Professor William Arrowsmith: "Euripedes' The Bacchae, or God Isn't Dead but Mad," 1968, Audio reel (¼ in.) (Box 9, Audio 2)
    - Lecture on the Exhibition "Hang Ups and Put Downs," 1968, Audio reel (¼ in.) (Box 9, Audio 3)
    - Orchestra Concert, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Play, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Press Releases, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Programs, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Proposal, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Sculpture, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Symposium on the Arts The Arts in an Age of Violence, 1968, Audio reel (¼ in.) (Box 9, Audio 4)
  - Inaugural Week of Fine Arts Center, Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Visual Art
    - Advisory Committee, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Art Collection Controversy/Solution, 1997-2001 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
    - Art Collection Move, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Art Collections Focus Groups, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Art Gallery or Fine Arts Gallery, 1972-1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Art History Gallery, 1982-2005 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Art Museum Advisory Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Art Museum Fundraising Committee, 1985-1994 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Art Museum Policy Committee
      - 1983-1999 (Box 23, Folder 15-20)
      - 1999 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Art Museum Policy Statements, 1984-1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Computer Audit and Needs Analysis, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/General, 1974-2004 (Box 24, Folder 4-16)
    - Dedication/Opening, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Director and Curator Positions, 1998-2008 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Disposal of Works of Art, Resolution, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1979-1986 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - General Information, 1997-2008 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Internal Audit of Fine Arts Galleries, 1976-1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Internal Audit of UWM Art Museum, 1976-1986 (Box 24, Folder 23-24)
    - Internal Audit, Stewardship of UW Art, Science, and Special Library Collections, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Philip/Greene Museum Proposal, 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Name Change, From UWM Art Museum to INOVA, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters, 1984-1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Permanent Collection, 1973-1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Rosenberg Bequest and Collection, 1974-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Task Force on the Status and Future of the UWM Art Museum, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
    - Volunteers, Handbook and Memorandum, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Integrated Arts and Sciences Program Proposal, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Inter-Arts Camp Projections, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Inter-Institutional Agreements & UW-Extension Arts Development, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - International Baccalaureate Diploma Programs, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Art Lecture, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Community's Sesquicentennial, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Kenilworth Building, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Knapp Bequest Committee, 1965-1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Lectures Committee, 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Lincoln Center for the Arts
    - 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32-33)
    - 1979-1984 (Box 20, Folder 13-18)
  - Literature and the Other Arts Symposium, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Marketing Task Force, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Martha Graham Dance Company, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Master of Fine Arts Degree
    - Planning Committee
      - 1973-1997 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - 1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Program Study, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Proposal Drafts
      - 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 22-23)
      - First Review by UW System Administration, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Documentation, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Submitted to UW System, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - Mayor's Council on the Arts, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Public Support for Cultural Organizations, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Merce Cunningham Dance Company Performance, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Meredith Monk Dance Company Performance, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Metropolitan Arts Council, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Metropolitan Arts Program
    - 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - Planning Document, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Milwaukee Artists Foundation, 1982-1993 (Box 21, Folder 8-10)
  - Milwaukee Ballet Company
    - 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Concert, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Milwaukee County Radio and Television Council, 1956-1964 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Milwaukee High School of the Arts, 1984-2004 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Milwaukee Institute of Art and Design, 1987-1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Milwaukee Public Schools
    - 1977-1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Arts Specialty Schools Collaboration, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Milwaukee's Sesquicentennial, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Minority Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Minority Retention, 1968-1982 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Mitchell Hall Remodling, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Music Opportunities Day, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Self-Survey Report
    - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - National Conference of Fine Arts Deans, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education Report, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - National Dance Company of Senegal, 1974-1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - National Invitational Crafts Symposium, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)